So I just had a woman come in my DMs and say that housing appraisals are not racist. That is a,
that the appraisal industry is not racist and that that is a wildly inaccurate statement
because she is an appraiser. She's definitely not a white woman. I don't know if she's black. I don't
know, like she could have been Latina, but I was like, ma'am. So then I sent her not one, not two,
not three, not four, but five different examples of black people having to whitewash their homes and
getting a higher appraisal than they did when their homes represented as black homes. It also
included a link to a whole documentary about how appraisals are racist. I did all of that. And she
wrote me back three paragraphs about how I was not only wrong, but I was ignorant to suggest
that appraising in America is racist, that the issue is really the banks, not the appraisers.
Anything having to do with any system in America is inherently racist. So that's one. Two,
particularly as it relates to housing, you arguing that they literally had to pass a housing act in
order for black people to have fair housing. So I don't know how you can somehow suggest that there
is any part of the housing industry that isn't racist. I'm talking from appraisals to the banks,
to the loan people that are even helping you get the loan. All of it has the capacity to be racist,
even if you individually are not. I blocked her. So she ain't seeing this message, but understand this
when you state something and then someone shows you empirical evidence that is contrary to your
understanding. You have to sit back and say, well, maybe I need to do more research. You don't stand
on it. That is the definition of willful ignorance, which is plaguing this nation immensely at present.
The age of idiocy continues.